Guide to the Yehuda Amichai Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1944-1999; Series I; 5.63; (14 boxes)
  - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE
    - Förderverein Deutscher Schriftsteller in Hessen, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 172)
    - Fortunoff Video Archive for Holocaust Testimonies, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 173)
    - Forward, 1995 May 5 (Box 4, Folder 174)
    - Four Winds Press, 1992 Jan 28 (Box 4, Folder 175)
    - France. Ministère de la culture, 1994, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 176)
    - Frank, Yitzchak, 1980 Nov 19 (Box 4, Folder 177)
    - Frick, Hans, 1978 Nov 21 (Box 4, Folder 178)
    - Fried, Philip, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 179)
    - Friedrich-Ebert Stiftung, 1995 Mar 27 (Box 4, Folder 180)
    - Fu, Hau, 1990-1994, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 181)
      Includes poems by Fu and translations
    - Fulda (Germany), 1997 Oct 7 (Box 4, Folder 182)
    - "G" General, 1977-1997, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 183-184)
    - Gableutz, Otto von der, 1993 Jun 7 (Box 4, Folder 185)
    - Gale Research Inc., 1989 Nov 21 (Box 4, Folder 186)
    - Galway Arts Centre, 1995 May 17 (Box 4, Folder 187)
    - Ganani-Elad, Devorah, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 188)
      Includes poem
    - Gao, Qiufu, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 189)
    - Garcia, Rachel, 1996-1998, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 190)
    - Gato, Bentsiyon, ha-Kihen, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 191)
    - Gehring-Münzel, Ursula, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 192)
    - George Mason University, 1989 Oct 16 (Box 5, Folder 193)
    - Germany (West). Botschaft (Israel), 1982-1995 (Box 5, Folder 194)
    - Gesellschaft für Christlich-Jüdische Zusammenarbeit Aachen, 1991 Sep 4 (Box 5, Folder 195)
    - Gilboa, Amir, 1980 Jul (Box 5, Folder 196)
    - Gilevski, Paskal, 1995 Apr 14 (Box 5, Folder 197)
    - Gill, James, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 198)
    - Gilman, Ernest B., 1987 Dec 2 (Box 5, Folder 199)
    - Goethe-Institut Düsseldorf, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 200)
    - Goethe-Institut Jerusalem, 1993-1997 (Box 5, Folder 201)
    - Goethe-Institut Tel-Aviv, 1989, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 202)
    - Gold, Nili Sharf, 1990-1997, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 203)
    - Goldstein, Brigitte, 1994 Dec 30 (Box 5, Folder 204)
    - Gouri, Haim, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 205)
    - Gratz College (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1966 Sep 20 (Box 5, Folder 206)
    - Greenberg, Helen [Medwedeff?], 1990 Dec 4 (Box 5, Folder 207)
    - Gregor-Dellin, Martin, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 208)
    - Grumen, Elinor, 1977-1983 (Box 5, Folder 209)
    - Gutmann, Assia, 1967-1968, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 210)
    - "H" General, 1969-1998, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 211-212)
    - ha-Aretz, 1994, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 213)
    - Haber, Leo, 1993 Nov 9 (Box 5, Folder 214)
      Includes poems by Haber
    - Haberkamm, Helmut, 1992 Oct 6 (Box 5, Folder 215)
    - Hachette (Firm), 1994 Jun 7 (Box 5, Folder 216)
    - Hadassah International Research Institute on Jewish Women, 1981 Nov 8 (Box 5, Folder 217)
    - Haifa (Israel), 1990, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 218)
    - Halevi-Zwick, Judith, 1978 Nov 1 (Box 5, Folder 219)
    - Hallaq, Boutros, 1988 Jun 6 (Box 5, Folder 220)
    - Hamahlalah l'chinuch Ash David Eylon, 1986-1992 (Box 5, Folder 221)
    - Hamahlakah leh kishrei Tirbut ve Medah, 1980-1986 (Box 5, Folder 222)
    - Hamenaka, Sheila, 1994 May 29 (Box 5, Folder 223)
    - Hammer, Reuven, 1993 Aug 11 (Box 5, Folder 224)
    - Hampl, Patricia, 1995 May 10 (Box 5, Folder 225)
    - Hannsmann, Margarete, 1992 Jun 7 (Box 5, Folder 226)
    - Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, 1988 Sep 15 (Box 5, Folder 227)
    - Harnik, Rayah, [1970?] Oct 27 (Box 5, Folder 228)
    - Harper & Row, Publishers, 1967-1990, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 229)
    - HarperCollins (Firm), 1990, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 230)
    - Harshav, Benjamin, 1985-1996 (Box 5, Folder 231)
    - Harvard University. Dept. of Near Eastern Languages & Civilization, 1981 Mar 10 (Box 5, Folder 232)
    - Harvard University. Graduate School of Design, 1980-1990 (Box 5, Folder 233)
    - Hashomer Hatzair, 1989-1995, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 234)
    - Hay Festival of Literature and the Arts Ltd., 1993-1995, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 235)
    - Hebrew Union College - Jewish Institute of Religion, 1988-1993, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 236)
    - Herlitz, Esther, 1993, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 237)
    - Herscher, Uri D., 1993 Aug 10 (Box 5, Folder 238)
    - Hessisches Literatur Büro im Mousonturm, 1991-1998 (Box 5, Folder 239)
    - Hevrah la-haganat ha-teva, 1995-1997 (Box 5, Folder 240)
    - Hirsch, Edward, 1981 Jun 16 (Box 5, Folder 241)
    - Hollander, John (Box 5, Folder 242)
    - Holzer, Madeline, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 243)
    - Hugh Lauter Levin Associates, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 244)
    - Hughes, Carol, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 245)
    - Hughes, Olwyn, 1967-1990, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 246)
    - Hughes, Ted, 1944-1997, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 247)
    - "I" General, 1977-1996, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 248)
    - Igud ha-kompozitorim be-Yisrael, 1975 Feb 13 (Box 6, Folder 249)
    - India. Dept. of Culture, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 250)
    - India. Embassy (Israel), 1995 Oct 30 (Box 6, Folder 251)
    - Indiana University Press, 1995 Sep 11 (Box 6, Folder 252)
    - Institut national des langues et civilisations orientales, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 253)
    - International Center for Peace in the Middle East, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 254)
    - International Congress of the P.E.N. Clubs, 1975-1994 (Box 6, Folder 255)
    - International Design Conference in Aspen, 1984 Dec 6 (Box 6, Folder 256)
    - International Institute for Secular Humanistic Judaism, 1986-1997 (Box 6, Folder 257)
    - International Parliament of Writers, 1994-1995, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 258)
    - International Poets Festival, 1982-1997 (Box 6, Folder 259)
    - International Writers' Conference, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 260)
    - Iranyi, Gabriel, 1987, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 261)
    - Irgun ole Merkaz Eropah, 1983 Mar (Box 6, Folder 262)
    - Ir Shalem - Jerusalem, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 263)
    - Israel Association for Secular Humanistic Judaism, 1995, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 264)
    - Israel. Merkaz ha-hasbarah, 1982 Mar 12 (Box 6, Folder 265)
    - Israel. Misrad ha-hinukh, ha-tarbut veha-sport, 1968-1999, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 266)
    - Israel. Misrad ha-huts, 1971-1998, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 267-268)
      Includes third party letter
    - Israel. Misrad ha-mada veha-omanuyot, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 269)
    - Israel. Misrad rosh ha-memshalah, 1993-1998 (Box 6, Folder 270)
    - Israel Psychiatric Association, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 271)
    - Israel. Rashut ha-shidur, 1966-1994, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 272)
    - Israel. Shagrirut (China), 1993 (Box 6, Folder 273)
    - Israel. Shagrirut (Denmark), 1988 Jun 30 (Box 6, Folder 274)
    - Israel. Shagrirut (Dominican Republic), 1991 Sep 19 (Box 6, Folder 275)
      Includes clipping
    - Israel. Shagrirut (France), 1981, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 276)
    - Israel. Shagrirut (Germany: West), 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 277)
    - Israel. Shagrirut (Great Britian), 1986-1995 (Box 6, Folder 278)
    - Israel. Shagrirut (India), 1993 Nov 11 (Box 6, Folder 279)
    - Israel. Shagrirut (Japan), 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 280)
      Includes third party correspondence
    - Israel. Shagrirut (Netherlands), 1991 Jul 29 (Box 6, Folder 281)
    - Israel. Shagrirut (Norway), 1995 Mar 8 (Box 6, Folder 282)
    - Israel. Shagrirut (Spain), 1994 Jul 26 (Box 6, Folder 283)
    - Israel. Shagrirut (Switzerland), 1981, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 284)
    - Israel. Shagrirut (United States), 1972 Aug 15 (Box 6, Folder 285)
    - Israel. Tseva haganah le-Yisra'el, 1968 Mar 15 (Box 6, Folder 286)
    - Israeli Academic Center in Cairo, 1985-1996 n.d. (Box 6, Folder 287)
    - Iton 77, 1982 Aug 4 (Box 6, Folder 288)
    - "J" General, 1964-1995, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 289)
    - Jablonska, Renata, 1997 Oct 6 (Box 6, Folder 290)
    - Jacobs, Yaakov, 1996 Jun 19 (Box 6, Folder 291)
      Includes poem by Jacobs
    - Jacoby, Herzel, 1995, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 292)
    - Jakob, Doris, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 293)
    - Jerusalem, 1986-1997, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 294)
    - Jerusalem International Book Fair, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 295)
    - The Jerusalem Post, 1995 May 28 (Box 6, Folder 296)
    - Jerusalem Print Workshop, 1996 Aug 19 (Box 6, Folder 297)
    - Jewish Agency for Israel, 1978, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 298)
    - Jewish Book Council, 1983, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 299)
    - Jewish National Fund, 1994 Oct 2 (Box 7, Folder 300)
    - Jewish Public Library (Montréal, Québec), 1989 Oct 16 (Box 7, Folder 301)
    - Jewish Publication Society of America, 1982-1996 (Box 7, Folder 302)
    - John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts, 1997 Dec 19 (Box 7, Folder 303)
    - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1989 Dec 11 (Box 7, Folder 304)
    - Jong, Erica, 1974-1995, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 305)
      Includes printed version of Jong's poem "Holding onto the Light?
    - Joris, Pierre, 1996 May 7 (Box 7, Folder 306)
    - Joseph, Lawrence, 1986-1993 (Box 7, Folder 307)
    - Josephy, Marcia Reines, 1990 Feb 16 (Box 7, Folder 308)
    - Journées de Mondorf, 1995 Mar 15 (Box 7, Folder 309)
    - "K" General, 1974-1997, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 310)
    - Kalvari, Gidon, 1997 Oct 13 (Box 7, Folder 311)
    - Kasdorf, Julia, 1992 Apr 2 (Box 7, Folder 312)
    - Kasemaa, Kalle, 1995 Feb 20 (Box 7, Folder 313)
    - Kasher, Asa, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 314)
    - Katan, Dina, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 315)
    - Kavanagh, P.J. (Patrick Joseph), 1976-1979 n.d. (Box 7, Folder 316)
    - Keren Hayesod, 1993 Nov 15 (Box 7, Folder 317)
    - Keren li-Yerushalayim, 1990-1997, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 318)
    - Keshet Broadcasting, 1996 Apr (Box 7, Folder 319)
    - Kevutsat Zamir Bar-Lev, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 320)
    - Kibuts ha-dati (Israel), 1990 (Box 7, Folder 321)
    - Kibuts ha-meuhad, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 322)
    - Kibuts Negbah (Israel), 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 323)
    - [Kinnell?], Galway, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 324)
    - Kirchway, Karl, 1992 Nov 17 (Box 7, Folder 325)
    - Klehr, Edwin H.; Klehr, Judith, 1982, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 326)
    - Klein, George, 1988-1992, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 327)
    - Klimenko, Alexandre A. (Box 7, Folder 328)
    - Kohler, Oliver, 1993, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 329)
    - Kokusai Banka Kaikan (Tokyo, Japan), n.y. Feb 15 (Box 7, Folder 330)
    - Kollek, Teddy, 1981-1996, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 331)
      Related Archival Materials note
      See also: Tnuat Yerushalayim Ahat, Box 11, folder 538
    - Koren, Gidi, 1974 Aug 5 (Box 7, Folder 332)
    - Korzeniowski, Tomasz, 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 333)
    - Kovenski, Idit, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 334)
    - Kozodoy, Neal, 1983 Apr 8 (Box 7, Folder 335)
    - Kreuz Verlag GmbH, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 336)
    - Kühner, H. O., 1982 Sep 30 (Box 7, Folder 337)
    - Kulturamt Freiburg (Freiburg im Breisgau, Germany), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 338)
    - "L" General, 1961-1997, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 339-340)
    - Lannan Foundation, 1990 Oct, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 341)
    - Lapkin, Sharon, 1991 Dec 31 (Box 7, Folder 342)
    - Leman, Gerard, 1991-1995 (Box 7, Folder 343)
    - Lerner, Moti, 1989 Nov 23 (Box 7, Folder 344)
    - Levi, Ron, 1966 Dec 4 (Box 7, Folder 345)
    - Library of Congress, 1969-1985 (Box 7, Folder 346)
    - Liepman AG, 1981-1986 (Box 7, Folder 347)
    - Linsel, Anne, 1995 Apr 4 (Box 7, Folder 348)
    - Lions International, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 349)
    - Lipson-Weller, Carolyn, 1995 Mar 23 (Box 7, Folder 350)
    - Literarisches Colloquium Berlin, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 351)
    - London Weekend Television, Ltd., 1986 (Box 7, Folder 352)
    - Lyman, Henry, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 353)
    - "M" General, 1965-1997, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 354-355)
    - Ma, Gao Ming, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 356)
      Includes fax of drawing of Amichai
    - Maaleh (Organization: Jeruslaem), n.d. (Box 8, Folder 357)
    - Maariv, 1981-1991 (Box 8, Folder 358)
    - Mahler, Sophia, 1997 Dec 24 (Box 8, Folder 359)
    - Makhon le-musikah Yisreelit, 1991 Feb 12 (Box 8, Folder 360)
    - Makhon le-tirgum sifrut Ivrit (Israel), 1969-1996 (Box 8, Folder 361-364)
    - Maoz, Ruti, 1994, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 365)
    - Marcus, Eliezer, 1996 Nov 17 (Box 8, Folder 366)
    - Marcus, J. Shlomo, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 367)
    - Margalit, Ruth, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 368)
    - Martiny, Anke, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 369)
    - Mazor, Yair, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 370)
    - McCullough, Frances, 1969, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 371)
    - McGraw-Hill Companies, 1999 Oct 25 (Box 8, Folder 372)
    - McHugh, Heather, 1990-1993, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 373)
    - Mekhon Vaitsman le-mada, 1991 Oct 3 (Box 8, Folder 374)
    - Mekhon Van Lir bi-Yerushalayim, 1995 Dec 7 (Box 8, Folder 375)
    - Menotti, Gian Carlo, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 376)
    - Merchavia, Ch., n.d. (Box 8, Folder 377)
    - Merian, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 378)
    - Michigan Quarterly Review, 1982-1995 (Box 8, Folder 379)
    - Midreshet Sedeh Boker, n.y. Dec 26 (Box 8, Folder 380)
    - Mifleget ha-avodah ha-Yisreelit, 1992 Jun 18 (Box 8, Folder 381)
      Includes printout of article and speech
    - Migdal David (Museum: Jerusalem), 1995 Dec 22 (Box 8, Folder 382)
    - Mindlin, M. (Murray), 1973-1982 (Box 8, Folder 383)
    - Mishkenot shaananim, 1986-1995 (Box 8, Folder 384)
    - Miss America Pageant, 1997 Feb 24 (Box 8, Folder 385)
    - Mitchell, Stephen, 1984, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 386)
    - Mitokh-Meler, Ednah, 1996, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 387)
    - Mizrahi, Mosheh, 1992 Oct 17 (Box 8, Folder 388)
    - Moment, 1988-1995 (Box 8, Folder 389)
    - Montenegro, David, 1991 Sep 15 (Box 8, Folder 390)
    - Mooij, Martin, 1977-1998 (Box 9, Folder 391)
    - Mosler, Peter, 1992, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 392)
      Includes poem by Mosler
    - Moss, Stanley, 1985, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 393)
    - Mucharik, Mario, 1988 Feb 19 (Box 9, Folder 394)
    - Muir, Sharona, 1994 Aug 7 (Box 9, Folder 395)
    - Müller, Karlheinz, 1992, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 396)
    - Muzeon Erets-Yisrael (Tel Aviv, Israel), 1993, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 397)
    - Muzeon Hertseliyah le-omanut, 1993 Jan 6 (Box 9, Folder 398)
    - Muzeon Yisrael (Jerusalem), 1981-1995, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 399)
    - "N" General, 1982-1996 (Box 9, Folder 400)
    - Narkiss, Uzi, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 401)
    - National Arts Council (Singapore), 1993 May 13 (Box 9, Folder 402)
    - National Foundation for Jewish Culture (U.S.A.), 1996 Dec 2 (Box 9, Folder 403)
    - National Geographic, 1982 Jan 5 (Box 9, Folder 404)
    - National Public Radio (U.S.A), 1996 Mar 12 (Box 9, Folder 405)
    - National University of Singapore. Centre for the Arts, 1995 May 25 (Box 9, Folder 406)
      Includes poems by Edwin Thumboo
    - Neiger, Mordechai (Motti), 1993 Sep 1 (Box 9, Folder 407)
    - Netherlands. Nationale UNESCO- Commissie, 1984, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 408)
    - Netzer, Y., 1972 Apr 6 (Box 9, Folder 409)
    - New York City Transit Authority, 1994 Apr 18 (Box 9, Folder 410)
    - New York University, 1984-1996 (Box 9, Folder 411)
    - Nieuw Israëlietisch Weekblad, 1978 Apr 13 (Box 9, Folder 412)
    - Nordbrandt, Henrik (Box 9, Folder 413)
    - Norddeutscher Rundfunk, 1965 Feb 26 (Box 9, Folder 414)
    - North Carolina. Dept. of Cultural Resources, 1995 Oct 17 (Box 9, Folder 415)
    - Nye, Naomi Shihab, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 416)
    - "O" General, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 417)
    - [O'Grady?], Desmond, 1991 Sep 17 (Box 9, Folder 418)
    - Ohalei Palmach Association, 1988-1997 (Box 9, Folder 419)
    - Olmert, Ehud, 1995 Jul (Box 9, Folder 420)
    - Ophir, Moshe, 1989 May 4 (Box 9, Folder 421)
    - Oppen, Mary, 1988 Apr 25 (Box 9, Folder 422)
    - Or'am Publishing House, 1990 Jan 12 (Box 9, Folder 423)
    - Oxford University Press, 1979-1993 (Box 9, Folder 424)
    - Oz, Amos, 1972-1985, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 425)
    - Ozick, Cynthia, 1984 May (Box 9, Folder 426)
    - "P" General, 1970-1999, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 427)
    - Papp, Alexander von (Box 9, Folder 428)
    - Parfitt, Tudor, 1982 Oct 11 (Box 9, Folder 429)
    - Pastan, Linda (Box 9, Folder 430)
    - Peled, Micha X, 1996 Sep 30 (Box 9, Folder 431)
    - Penguin Books, 1969-1996 (Box 9, Folder 432)
    - Pepper, Anshil, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 433)
    - Peres, Shimon, 1986, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 434)
    - Perrie, Walter, 1981 Jul 4 (Box 9, Folder 435)
    - Pincas, Israel, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 436)
    - Pioneer Women (Organization: U.S.), 1989 Dec 5 (Box 9, Folder 437)
    - POETRY, 1980 Dec (Box 9, Folder 438)
    - Poetry Book Society, 1967-1992 (Box 9, Folder 439)
    - Poetry Review, 1992 Jun 2 (Box 9, Folder 440)
    - Poetry Society of America, 1991 Feb 25 (Box 9, Folder 441)
    - Poets House (Firm), 1992 Sep 2 (Box 9, Folder 442)
    - Polukhina, Valentina, 1998 Jul 14 (Box 9, Folder 443)
    - Popa, Vesko, 1971-1973 (Box 9, Folder 444)
    - Prometteo, 1995-1999 (Box 9, Folder 445)
    - Princeton University, 1987 Jun 11 (Box 9, Folder 446)
    - Pushcart Press, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 447)
    - Pyramid Creations, 1994, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 448)
    - Quarry West, 1986-1988 (Box 9, Folder 449)
    - "R" General, 1966-1999, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 450)
    - R.A.L. Laskov Officer Training School, 1995-1997 (Box 10, Folder 451)
    - R. Piper & Co., 1986-1996 (Box 10, Folder 452)
    - Rabin, Yitzhak, 1993-1994, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 453)
    - Rankin, David (Box 10, Folder 454)
    - Raphael, Chaim, 1989 Mar 19 (Box 10, Folder 455)
    - Rav-Hon, Orna, 1996 Nov 27 (Box 10, Folder 456)
    - Richter, Milan, 1997 Mar 10 (Box 10, Folder 457)
      Includes poem by Richter
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 458)
    - Roe, Yale, 1993 Aug 5 (Box 10, Folder 459)
    - Rónai, Cora, 1990 Dec 1 (Box 10, Folder 460)
    - Rosenmeyer, Thomas G., 1991 Oct 3 (Box 10, Folder 461)
    - Rosenthal, Mack, 1974-1991 (Box 10, Folder 462)
    - Roshovski, Leah, 1992 May 18 (Box 10, Folder 463)
    - Rottenbach, Bruno, 1982-1986 (Box 10, Folder 464)
      Includes poem by Rottenbach
    - Royal Festival Hall (London, England), 1999 Oct 29 (Box 10, Folder 465)
    - "S" General, 1969-1999, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 466-468)
    - Safdie, Moshe, 1985-1995 (Box 10, Folder 469)
    - San Diego State University, 1983 Mar 21 (Box 10, Folder 470)
    - San Francisco State University. Poetry Center, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 471)
    - Sanders, Ronald, 1986 Jun 26 (Box 10, Folder 472)
    - Sanguineti, Edoardo, 1988 Dec 2 (Box 10, Folder 473)
    - Schädlich, Hans Joachim, 1992 Apr 9 (Box 10, Folder 474)
    - Schechtman, Maty, 1989-1995 (Box 10, Folder 475)
    - Schiff, Alvin I., 1968 Oct 24 (Box 10, Folder 476)
    - Schiller, Ariel, 1994 Nov 28 (Box 10, Folder 477)
    - Schimmel, Harold, 1975-1994, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 478)
    - Schindel, Robert, 1992 Apr 10 (Box 10, Folder 479)
    - Schmidt, Shira Leibowitz, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 480)
    - Schmitt, Eleonore, 1994 May 7 (Box 10, Folder 481)
    - Schocken Publishing House, 1985-1998 (Box 10, Folder 482)
    - Schultz, Philip, 1984-1994, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 483)
    - Schwarcz, Vera, 1991-1993 (Box 10, Folder 484)
    - Schwartz, Perla, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 485)
      Includes printed version of poem by Schwartz
    - Schweizer Fernsehen DRS, 1993 Sep 13 (Box 10, Folder 486)
    - Seghers, Colette, 1997 Oct (Box 10, Folder 487)
    - Sexton, Anne, 1970 Feb 11 (Box 10, Folder 488)
    - Shalev, Meir, 1989, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 489)
    - Shalom India-Israel Centre, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 490)
    - Shalom, Shin, 1969, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 491)
    - Shammas, Anton, 1973 Dec 18 (Box 10, Folder 492)
    - Shazar, Zalman, 1969 Apr 14 (Box 10, Folder 493)
    - Sheep Meadow Press, 1986-1997 (Box 10, Folder 494)
    - Shem Tov, Viktor, 1995 Dec 8 (Box 10, Folder 495)
    - Shestack, Jerome J., 1977-1995, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 496)
    - Shiraishi, Yazuko, 1990-1993 n.d. (Box 10, Folder 497)
    - Shofet, Asher, 1982 Jun 29 (Box 10, Folder 498)
    - Shorer, Zion, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 499)
    - Shultz, Philip, 1990 Oct 20 (Box 10, Folder 500)
    - Sigal, Clancy, 1977 Jul 24 (Box 10, Folder 501)
    - Sillitoe, Alan, 1977-1994 (Box 10, Folder 502)
    - Sillitoe, Ruth, 1988-1994 (Box 10, Folder 503)
    - Sirat, René-Samuel, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 504)
    - Sjöstrand, Östen, 1982 Jul 24 (Box 10, Folder 505)
    - Sklarew, Myra, 1980-1995, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 506)
    - Sobrino, Gabriella, 1967 Jun 17 (Box 10, Folder 507)
    - Sociedad Hebraica Argentina, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 508)
    - Söderberg, Lasse, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 509)
    - Someck, Ronny, 1989, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 510)
    - Sonora Review, 1980 Dec 30 (Box 11, Folder 511)
    - Sorescu, Marin, 1985 Jun 1 (Box 11, Folder 512)
    - Sotheby's (Firm), 1983, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 513)
    - South Bank Centre, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 514)
    - Staay, Adriaan von der, 1972-1990, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 515)
    - Stadtler, Bea, 1967 Apr 7 (Box 11, Folder 516)
    - Stahl, Nanette, 1994 Mar 8 (Box 11, Folder 517)
    - Starkman, Elaine, 1980 May 30 (Box 11, Folder 518)
      Includes draft of introduction
    - State University of New York College at Purchase, 1990 May 3 (Box 11, Folder 519)
    - Steidle, Hans, 1995 Jan 17 (Box 11, Folder 520)
    - Stern, Frederick C., 1987 Aug 10 (Box 11, Folder 521)
    - Stone, Michael H., 1979 Apr 20 (Box 11, Folder 522)
    - Striar, Marguerite M., 1993 (Box 11, Folder 523)
    - Struski veceri na poezijata, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 524)
    - Süddeutscher Rundfunk, 1978, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 525)
    - Südwestfunk (Baden-Baden, Germany), 1990 Jan 3 (Box 11, Folder 526)
    - Svenska akademien, 1989, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 526a)
      Includes third-party letter to Schocken Publishing House
    - Swados, Elizabeth, 1986, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 527)
    - "T" General, 1966-1999 (Box 11, Folder 528)
    - Tel Aviv (Israel), 1964-1990 (Box 11, Folder 529)
    - Tel Aviv Review, 1990 Jan 9 (Box 11, Folder 530)
    - Tenuah le-Yahadut mitkademet be- Yisrael, 1983 Aug 9 (Box 11, Folder 531)
    - Tharp, Twyla, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 532)
    - Theodore Presser Company, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 533)
    - Thomas J. Watson, Jr. Institute for International Studies (Brown University), 1996 Sep 26 (Box 11, Folder 534)
    - Tichy, Susan, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 535)
    - Time-Life Books, 1991 Jul 1 (Box 11, Folder 536)
    - The Times Literary Supplement, 1988 Jun 20 (Box 11, Folder 537)
    - Tnuat Yerushalayim Ahat, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 538)
    - Tomlinson, Charles, 1990 Jan 8 (Box 11, Folder 539)
    - Topiwala, Chandrakant, 1996-1997, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 540)
    - Tranströmer, Tomas, 1989 Jul 3 (Box 11, Folder 541)
    - Trumeh, 1999 Dec 13 (Box 11, Folder 542)
    - Tucson Poetry Festival, 1994-1998 (Box 11, Folder 543)
    - Twite, Robin, 1993 Jul 15 (Box 11, Folder 544)
    - Tzovah (Israel), 1973 May 9 (Box 11, Folder 545)
    - "U", General (Box 11, Folder 546)
    - Udruzenje knjizevnika Srbije, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 547)
    - Unesco, 1994 Jan 20 (Box 11, Folder 548)
    - United Israel Appeal, 1994-1997 (Box 11, Folder 549)
    - United Nations, 1992 Aug 20 (Box 11, Folder 550)
    - United States. Dept. of State, 1975 Sep 29 (Box 11, Folder 551)
    - United States. Embassy (Israel), 1971-1988 (Box 11, Folder 552)
    - United States. White House Office, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 553)
    - United Synagogue of Conservative Judaism, 1996 May 6 (Box 11, Folder 554)
    - Universitah ha-Ivrit bi-Yerushalayim, 1974-1998, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 555-556)
    - Universitat Hefah, 1989-1995 (Box 11, Folder 557)
    - Universität Siegen, 1992 Jan 16 (Box 11, Folder 558)
    - Universitat Tel-Aviv, 1978-1998, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 559)
      Includes printed essay by Amichai
    - Université des sciences humaines de Strasbourg, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 560)
    - University of Arizona. Poetry Center, 1980 Feb 16 (Box 11, Folder 561)
    - University of British Columbia, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 562)
    - University of California, Berkeley, 1975-1997 (Box 11, Folder 563)
    - University of California, Los Angeles, 1992 Feb 25 (Box 11, Folder 564)